Hello friends, in the previous video I
told you how you can avail the benefit of Rs 500 free of cost from Bajaj Pri membership.
Ok?
You will get a Flipkart gift voucher of ₹500
and what to say, you will get gas booking, mobile
recharge and many other things like those OTT
plans free of cost.  Meaning, for ₹500
you have to use ₹498 and out of that you will cover ₹700 on the same
day in a single day.
Ok?  So now let me tell you.  Look, let
me tell you that
another offer has come for those with Prime membership, free
spins.  Now if you spin it you can
get many offers of anything.  In this you
can again get a gift card of ₹500
from Flipkart and you can get anything else in it.
Like MNTRa, it has
Flipkart's OTT and Chinese Wise, that is, what all is there, so
you have to see how to do it in it.
As soon as we click on Spin Now,
see what we get in it.
As I spin this now I'll
show you what I'm going to get in this.
Ok?  So I mean you
can go and watch the previous video.  As I
told you, how will you get a Flipkart gift voucher of ₹500 free of cost
?  How can I
not get it?  We did a spin.  Now let me
show you what we get in this.
We got this for ₹100.  Something what he
got.  Got some reward.  We do some things
like bye.  If we have to answer this then
all of the above will come.
Ok?  Otherwise, everyone gets the same option.
Ok?  You can get up to ₹500 in this.  You can
get a gift card or Mtra voucher.
Anything can be found.  So
what happens to many people?  A gift card of ₹500 is
drawn.  These are all my
plans.  Ok?  Whatever I have
redeemed in this or am about to redeem.
It has a subscription to Gaana.
Received a Flipkart gift card voucher of ₹500.  Here
you will spin and earn, then on spinning
you will get that offer.  Ok?  Here is
my ₹100 offer that
I got, which has a validity of 30
days.  I have to use it within 30 days.
Otherwise, it will expire.
The date is written below each one.  Whichever
plan it is, which offer is valid for how many days.
You will get many benefits in this.
So it means that everyone should take it
without any hesitation and there is a
trick behind it as to
how you will get all these benefits.  You can watch my old
videos by going to my old videos.
Now I will show you
why I got this ₹50 cashback.
Ok?  By doing this, you
can also get ₹50 cashback every time.  I am
telling you that you will get Prime membership in this for ₹498.
But
you will easily earn ₹700-₹80 within 2 days.
Free of cost.  You should not feel anything.
Meaning there will be many benefits.
You will get OTTs.  You will
get subscriptions for the song.  You will keep
getting some cashback on everything.  Meaning you get
only benefits in this.  According to me,
you will definitely benefit from this up to ₹1500
and you get a one year and
3 months OTT plan.
Now what did I get these ₹50 for?
I will also show you this thing
in the next video.  Well then.
You must go and watch my previous video to know what
benefits you will get and how to redeem them.
You must have seen my balance behind.
113 was some rupees.  Then it became ₹163.
Increased directly by ₹50.
Ok?  Now after that I will tell you why this happened to me.
Ok?  You're
not getting that many backs.  This is causing back
problems.  One second.  So yes sir.
Now let us go to the next page.  Now
what happens on the next page is that
every Prime guy must do it on Spin Now.
We get many benefits from this.  How to apply
promo code etc. in its Prime membership
?
You can see it in my previous video.  Like
I had recharged it.  Ok?  I had this mobile
recharged for me.  I
got ₹50 cashback for that.  Cashback is not
available like this.  You straightened up.
Recharged the mobile.  You never
get cashback like this.  Ok?  So what do you have to do for that
?  Whenever you go for cashback
,
okay?  If you recharge your mobile then
you will automatically get offers etc. like
gas booking, electricity, bill payment, whatever you
do on it then you will
automatically get a promo code there.
After applying the promo code you have to make the payment.
You can see
my cashback came on 17th October.  And
you can see this recharge of VI.  It is not from VI.
What date is this?  You are showing this on 16th October,
right?  On 16th October I
recharged ₹300 for 29289.  That means
I am getting a refund of ₹50 on a recharge of ₹300.
Ok?  So you guys can also do this and
book gas for anyone using
your number.  Ok?  Recharge anyone's
mobile or pay anyone's
electricity bill.  There are many
benefits in this.  There will be more vouchers in this
which I will show in my future videos.
What do I say to you? Whenever you recharge
, book gas, or do anything, you should make the
payment first and then make the payment later.  Before making the payment,
you must check whether you have
entered the promo code correctly or not.
You must enter the promo code correctly.
Ok?  We had it recharged.  So
in return we
got a gift voucher of ₹50.  We got cashback
which gets used in our next
order etc.
Ok?  So friends, I hope
you enjoyed my video.
I will make many such informative videos.  If
you want videos related to loan on any thing
which has lowest interest loan then please
tell me.  I will
definitely make a video on that too.  See you
in the next video.  Until then, take
care of yourself and be happy.  Look, there are
many benefits of Prime membership.
People should definitely take it.  See you
in the next video.  Till then take
care of yourself.  Bye.  Good night.  All people are
happy